

Muhammad Mustafa

Frontend developer

I am resourceful front end web developer bringing in depth knowledge of latest technology trend to produce a website using react js for front-end and produce application using react native. Experience at handling code and extension to meet the organization front facing need.

mustafa128khan@gmail.com



Islamabad, Pakistan

03304628128

EDUCATION

Study Program **BS SOFTWARE ENGG**

Project

- Quran (app and web)

F.Sc

Hist College hangu

04/2016 - 04/2018

Matric

Hangu public School and College Hangu

03/2014 - 03/2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Eziline Software House

01/2024 - Present

Front End Developer Cruxdevs Pvt limited

09/2023 - 12/2023

Islamabad I-14

Islamabad

SKILLS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Quran app (react Native) FYP

Quran web (react js) FYP

Fruitable

Recipe Fund

Keerki

Ochenia

CERTIFICATES

Application developer

web developer

LANGUAGES

pashto

Full Professional Proficiency

urdu

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

games